Hi. I'm Juno.
大家好 我是 Juno
I'm Josh.
我是 Josh
We're here to share some tips on how to help you succeed in this nano degree program.
在这节视频里 我们想分享一些帮助你完成本次纳米学位的技巧
So, Josh, you've seen a lot of students go do this program. What's your advice?
Josh 在这个项目里你带过很多学员 你有什么好的建议吗？
Yes. So, I think one of the biggest things is to be successful in the program.
嗯 我认为 想要成功地完成本次课程
You have to be a really active learner.
最重要的是学会主动学习
What that means is not just watching all of the videos,
也就是说 不能只看视频
but also a lot of our most successful students take notes,
还要在适当的时候做笔记
and they take really good notes.
很多优秀的学员都做笔记 并且他们的笔记都做的很好
So, whether that's screenshots of the videos and then written
你可以对视频内容做截图
notes underneath on type out notes or for me,
然后在图片下面写下你的想法
I actually like just writing things in
或者像我那样 直接在平板电脑上做笔记
a notepad that I carry around with me and then I can look at later.
这样方便随时查看
Also, just when there's coding,
如果有编程的作业
writing the code yourself.
一定要自己写代码
So, I think one of the biggest things is you have to write code to learn how to code,
因为只有动手才能真正学会编程
and sometimes that's just a lot of repetition.
而且有些时候同样的代码会反复出现
Beyond that, there's a lot of things to do with
除了这两点 时间管理也很重要
time management and how do you manage your time to be a successful student?
作为学员 你该如何高效地管理自己的时间？
Sure. Managing time is definitely
是的 时间管理绝对
a very tricky component that has a big contribution to success.
是成功的重要要素
But what we've seen,
我们发现
is that students who are most successful,
那些学有所成的学员们
come to a classroom at least two times a week.
每周至少来教室学习两次
So, just making sure you make that habit of going to the classroom regularly,
也就说 要保证规律的学习时间
you can make a huge difference.
这对你的学习成效会有很大的帮助
There's lots of ways to do that.
有很多方法可以保证自己的学习时间
Yeah. Whether that's due like mobile apps or
是的 比如说 利用手机软件的提醒功能
just like blocking out times in your calendar,
或者在日程表里抽出专门的时间来学习
and just keeping that on your daily routine.
再或者把学习变成每天的习惯
But everything is dependent on your background,
但是所有这一切都取决于你个人的情况、
what your learning style is,
你的学习风格、
and which parts of the course might be newer to you or easier for you.
你对课程内容的熟悉程度
So, in the end,
总的来说
just getting to know what your pace is and setting expectations for
掌握自己的学习节奏 设置合理的目标
yourself and being open to adjusting your time estimations,
并且安排好时间
can really help you succeed in the program.
会对你成功完成本次的课程非常有帮助
So, sometimes, maybe a particular quiz in a lesson
有些时候 某些课的习题比其他课的习题更难
might take you a lot longer than other parts of the lesson.
会让你花费很多时间
Sometimes, this can be really good because it can help reinforce
但这不一定是件坏事 因为它会帮助你
your understanding and really develop your knowledge in that specific topic.
加深对知识点的理解
But sometimes, it could take way longer than you want to and it can be frustrating.
不过有些时候 也会让人比较沮丧
Do you have any advice on how to deal with these situations?
针对这种情况 你有什么建议吗？
Yeah. So, I'll call those blockers,
当然 这些叫做 blockers - 障碍
and I think we all get them.
相信我们大多数人都经历过这种情况
I think there's two big ways to address blockers.
我觉得 有两个解决办法
One is to use the community.
一个是利用我们的社群
There are students who just went through the content that you're going through,
里面有很多学员
who just had to learn this for the first time too.
他们曾经也遇到过你现在面临的问题
A lot of times, they can give really good advice for things outside of the classroom or
很多时候 他们都会给出问题答案的资料
specific texts components within the classroom
不管是教室里的文档、视频或者是外部的资源
that helped them really internalize an idea.
这对你内化这些知识非常有帮助
Then, the second thing is just being able to Google well.
第二个办法 就是学会用谷歌
Googling is a skill in of itself.
不得不说 用谷歌搜索本身是一门技能
I think that whether it's being able to take like
不管是为了寻找问题的解决方案
an error from your code and search it or read through the documentation,
阅读技术文档
or whether you're trying to really grasp a large project,
还是你想真正地理解某个项目
and you're looking through it entire blog posts or Quora post,
阅读技术博客文章或者是查找 Quora 上的答案
all of those things can help you better internalize the content
所有这些都对你解决问题本身和
and even solved just small snips that might be happening in your code.
真正地内化这些知识很有帮助
So, with that, do you have
以上就是我的建议
any final thoughts for students before they tackle their Nanodegree program?
你还有什么要补充的吗？
Yeah. So, we hope these tips can help you.
除了之前的建议 我还想说
But in the end, learning is really a mindset,
学习本身是一种心态
and everyone's going to struggle.
每个人多多少少都要付出努力
You have to go into this knowing that it's going to be challenging,
你需要抱着挑战高峰的心态去学习
and just making sure a patient with yourself
保持对自己的耐心
and determined to make sure this is the best learning experience for you,
并且坚信你正在学的内容会
can really help you succeed.
真正对你有所帮助
Yeah. So, thank you.
是的 谢谢
We hope that our tips can help you be successful with your Nanodegree program.
希望我们的建议能够帮助你成功地完成本课程的学习